kidzania.com 2016-05-13

# KidZania – Get Ready for a Better World

EFFECTIVE DATE: March 14th, 2013

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) governs the collection, use and sharing of Personal Information through KidZania.com and by any applications issued by by KidZania, S.A. de C.V. (“KidZania” or “We”), and its subsidiaries (each a “KidZania Company”) and KidZania authorized third party KZ Franchisees (“KZ Franchisees”). By using KidZania.com and/or a KidZania application, you indicate your acceptance of the terms of this Policy.

This Policy only applies to Personal Information. “Personal Information” refers to information that may be used to contact or identify an individual. This may include, but is not limited to, first and last name; street address; email address; telephone number; or other identifying information. In certain jurisdictions, a photo may be considered Personal Information. Personal Information may also include non-identifying information that may be stored with Personal Information.

Information that does not identify a person, such as anonymous or aggregated data, is not covered by this Policy. We may collect, use and disclose such information in order to evaluate and improve our service offerings; communicate to our sponsors, advertisers and KZ Franchisees; or for other purposes without limitation.

This Policy covers the KidZania.com website and any applications issued by KidZania. On our Site, we link to B-KidZanian.com, the website for the KidZania loyalty program, and individual websites for each KidZania location. B-KidZanian.com and the individual websites for different locations (“KZ Locations”) operated under the “KidZania” Brand which may include KidZania owned locations and/or KZ Franchisee owned locations may have their own privacy policies that govern your use of those sites. In addition, KidZania may link to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by a KidZania Company or Franchisee. These third-party websites may collect personal information about visitors. The information practices of such websites, organizations and or businesses, including those of our sponsors and commercial partners, are governed by the privacy policies on those websites and are not covered or governed by this Policy. KidZania does not endorse and is not responsible for the practices of these sites. We recommend that when you leave our Site, you check the privacy policies of each of the websites you view before providing personal information. This includes when you use an application on a mobile device to communicate personal information to a KidZania-operated or third party online service.

KidZania.com does not ask you to submit Personal Information or to register in order to view our Site. We do provide contact information so that you may contact us if you have questions or would like more information about KidZania. If you contact us by email or postal mail, we may use any Personal Information you provide to respond to your inquiry, to improve our customer service, and for other internal purposes. We will not use the information for marketing purposes.

KidZania may request minimal amounts of personal information in connection with the use of a KidZania application on a mobile device. However, unless the application is used to upload data to a KidZania website, online service, or a third party service, that information is stored only on the device and is not collected by KidZania. Due to concerns about younger users using applications to upload what may include personal information to the Internet, KidZania requires parents or guardians to consent to such use of the application by the minor before an upload to a KidZania website would be allowed. For more information, please see our Notice to Parents: Online Child Privacy.

KidZania may use technical means to collect certain non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our Site. We may also work with a third party service provider to collect similar information. To do this, KidZania companies and/or our service providers may use cookies or other technical measures to enable the collection of information and its correlation over time. The KidZania Companies, KidZania Franchisees and service providers will not combine anonymous data collected via the KidZania.com website with Personal Information.

  * **Log Information:** In order to permit your connection to the Site, our servers receive and record information about your computer and browser, such as your IP address, browser type, http referrer (where you visited KidZania from) and other software or hardware information. If you access KidZania from a mobile or other consumer electronic device, we may collect a unique device identifier (“UDID”) assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device.
  * **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:** We also use cookies and other tracking technologies (for example: browser cookies, pixels, and beacons), which are comprised of small bits of data that often incorporate an anonymous unique identifier. We use these technologies to learn about how visitors interact with our Site. Most browsers are set to accept cookies, but you can adjust your settings to block cookies. We do not use “permanent” cookies that survive after the user leaves the Site. To the extent that KidZania works with third parties for purposes of delivering, evaluating and improving online services, such third parties may use their own cookies or other technical measures to gather anonymous information about your use of the site. Any information independently collected by third parties via our site will be subject to that party’s privacy policy.

For more information about cookies or to stop accepting cookies, please see: OnGuardOnline’s Understanding Cookies at [www.onguardonline.gov.](http://onguardonline.gov/articles/0042-cookies-leaving-trail-web#Understanding%20Cookies)

KidZania may share Personal Information within the KidZania Companies and with KidZania Franchisees and service providers so that we may provide and manage the Site and our applications. For example, we may hire a third-party service provider or agent to help host the Site, help us with contests or promotions, or to serve advertising. Third-party service providers who work on behalf of KidZania must agree to only use Personal Information subject to this Policy to provide services to the KidZania Companies or an Operator.

KidZania, KidZania Companies, KidZania Franchisees, and third-party service providers may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:

  * To respond to your inquiries and provide customer support for your use of KidZania content and services available through our Site or applications.
  * To deliver relevant event notices, content, and advertisements for products, services, contests or promotions on behalf of KidZania, KidZania Companies, KZ Franchisees or sponsors.
  * To measure and improve your experience on the Site or with our applications.
  * In the event of a bankruptcy, or a merger, acquisition, joint venture or other business transaction, involving our Site and applications, Personal Information may be transferred as part of the assets of the company, but will remain subject to this Privacy Policy.

Additionally, Personal Information may be disclosed without prior notice when KidZania has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to protect or defend the legal rights or property of KidZania, other KidZania Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); to protect the safety and security of other KidZania users or members of the public; to protect the integrity of our Site; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process.

KidZania will not sell, rent, or share Personal Information with third parties for any reason other than those described above without first obtaining your consent.

Safety is a top priority for KidZania. We have implemented commercially reasonable policies and procedures to provide an appropriate level of security for the Personal Information that we collect and store. We require that any other third parties to whom we disclose Personal Information governed by this Policy implement similar safeguards to protect Personal Information.

KidZania gives you the option of editing or removing your Personal Information from KidZania systems. If you need to access, correct, or delete any Personal Information you have provided to KidZania, you may send an email request to [info@kidzania.com](mailto:info@kidzania.com).

From time to time, KidZania may update the Policy, as necessary, and will post the revised policy at <http://www.kidzania.com/privacy.php>. If we make material changes to the Policy that expand our rights to collect and/or use your Personal Information, we will notify you through the Site.

There are KZ Locations around the globe, and we recognize that the Personal Information we collect may be subject to protections under the laws of your country. Your Personal Information may be transferred or made available to and among KidZania Companies, Franchisees or service providers in other Locations around the world. Some of these countries may not require equivalent protections for Personal Information as exist under your local laws. By providing Personal Information to us, you acknowledge and consent to the processing, transfers, and disclosures described in this Policy. Any KidZania Companies or third parties who process data subject to this Policy are required to follow this Policy and appropriately protect your Personal Information.

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, please contact us at:

ATTN: KidZania.com Customer Service  
Juan Salvador Agraz 50, PH,  Col. Lomas de Santa Fe  
Cuajimalpa, Mexico D.F. C.P. 05348

KidZania provides the following information to notify parents of KidZania’s policies and practices for handling personal information that may be obtained from a minor at a KidZania Park, a KidZania application, or a KidZania online service.

  1. KidZania obtains in Park consent from parents and guardians to allow online interaction between minors and KidZania online services.
  2. KidZania has a policy of not collecting, using or disclosing personal information from minors except with prior parental consent, consent provided on behalf of a parental by an educational institution, or some other legal or policy basis for the collection (e.g. risk of imminent harm to a child). If a parent or guardian refuses to consent to the collection, use or disclosure of the information, KidZania will not collect, use or disclose the information.
  3. If a parent or guardian consents to use of a KidZania application, the child may take a photo of himself or herself which they may then customize using graphic elements provided by KidZania. KidZania may ask your child for basic biographical information such as first name, age or month/day of birth, gender, or country where the child resides or other non-specifically identifying information.
  4. If a parent or guardian further consents to the minor uploading the final image and biographical data to a KidZania-operated website, then KidZania may collect, use and disclose the image to other users of the application and website, third parties who may view the KidZania website, search engines or other technologies that catalog publicly available online content, partners and service providers. KidZania does not control and is not responsible for the policies and practices of third party sites where users of a KidZania application may post content.
  5. A parent may withdraw their consent at any time and request deletion of their child’s personal information from KidZania’s systems. If such a request is received, KidZania will remove any of the child’s content from public view, delete all copies of the child’s content, and refuse the child further access to the site.
  6. A parent may also request to review any personal information held by KidZania pertaining to their child and may request deletion of such information.

To withdraw consent, make a request for deletion of content or personal data, or to request review of personal data held on your child, you may contact KidZania at:

ATTN: KidZania.com Customer Service   
Juan Salvador Agraz 50, PH, Col. Lomas de Santa Fe  
Cuajimalpa, Mexico D.F. C.P. 05348  
Phone: +525591777600
